<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Physics on Sheng Feng</title>
    <link>http://sfeng77.github.io/tags/physics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Physics on Sheng Feng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Sheng Feng</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/physics/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>GeauxCTQMC</title>
      <link>http://sfeng77.github.io/project/cthyb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sfeng77.github.io/project/cthyb/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This project is sponsered by LA-SIGMA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;released-package&#34;&gt;Released Package&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.institute.loni.org/lasigma/package/cthyb/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;http://www.institute.loni.org/lasigma/package/cthyb/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;purpose&#34;&gt;Purpose&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Continuous Time Quantum Monte Carlo Impurity Solver, using the hybridization expansion algorithm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;systems&#34;&gt;Systems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This code has been tested on a computing system equipped with Intel Core i7-2600 CPU, Intel Xeon Phi 7120P co-processor, and Intel icc (ICC) 14.0.2 20140120 compiler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contents&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This package contains code and sample data for a Hybridization Expansion Continuous Time Quantum Monte Carlo Solver. The data generated from the code is tested against published results in literature. For the latest version and other resources visit &lt;a href=&#34;http://lasigma.loni.org/package/cthyb/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;http://lasigma.loni.org/package/cthyb/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgments&#34;&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The accelerator ports of this code were developed by Sheng Feng, Sam Irving, Roozbeh Karimi, Ka-Ming Tam, Jian Tao, Juana Moreno, J. Ramanujam, Mark Jarrell. This work was supported in part by the National Science Foundation under the NSF EPSCoR Cooperative Agreement No. EPS-1003897 with additional support from the Louisiana Board of Regents.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GeauxIsing</title>
      <link>http://sfeng77.github.io/project/geauxising/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sfeng77.github.io/project/geauxising/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This project is sponsered by LA-SIGMA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;released-package&#34;&gt;Released Package&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.institute.loni.org/lasigma/package/ising/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;http://www.institute.loni.org/lasigma/package/ising/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;purpose&#34;&gt;Purpose&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3d Edwards-Anderson Model simulation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;systems&#34;&gt;Systems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This package has been tuned for NVidia Graphics processing units (GPUs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contents&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This package contains the source code and sample data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgments&#34;&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The accelerator ports of this code were developed by Ye Fang, Sheng Feng, Ka-Ming Tam, Zhifeng Yun, Juana Moreno, J. Ramanujam, Mark Jarrell.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krylov</title>
      <link>http://sfeng77.github.io/project/krylov/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sfeng77.github.io/project/krylov/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This project is sponsered by LA-SIGMA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;released-package&#34;&gt;Released Package&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.institute.loni.org/lasigma/package/krylov/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;http://www.institute.loni.org/lasigma/package/krylov/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;purpose&#34;&gt;Purpose&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This code is a Krylov Solver using the Arnoldi iteration for Kanamori Hamiltonian. it is used for calculating the exponential of matrices in a Continuous Time Quantum Monte Carlo (CTQMC) solver on systems equipped with an intel Xeon Phi. This solver calculates the following quantity:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$exp(-H*t)*v$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;where:
H is a sparse matrix that represents the Kanamori Hamiltonian in the CTQMC solver. t is a scalar. v is a vector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;systems&#34;&gt;Systems&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The code was developed and tested on a computer equipped with the following software packages: Red Hat Enterprise Linux Version 6.6, GCC 4.4.7, intel ICC composer_xe_2013_sp1.1.106, and intel MKL composer_xe_2013_sp1.2.144.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contents&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The code provided here is a highly tuned implementation of the Krylov solver designed for a very specific hamiltonian matrix. This tool is comprised of two different codes, an initialization code which is executed on the CPU, and a Xeon Phi native library which is integrated in the main CTQMC code. This package also has a simple test using provided sample inputs (hamiltonians of 5 and 6 orbitals)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgments&#34;&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This code was developed by Roozbeh Karimi, Sheng Feng, Jian Tao, Ka-Ming Tam, David Koppelman, Juana Moreno, and Mark Jarrell. This work was supported in part by the National Science Foundation under the NSF EPSCoR Cooperative Agreement No. EPS-1003897 with additional support from the Louisiana Board of Regents.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
